(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-19T23:19:52.726790",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Ow!
Huh
Come chase me
Everyday I spent crying 'bout almost-loves turned complicated
On the way, yeah, my heart got torn up, shredded, all but dead, and
now they say I, I'm just a masochist, they're sick of it
Boy, take a hint, you ain't gon' ever get this
Pedal to the metal, shootin' straight to the stars
Got a cravin' like the danger on me
Up another level, temptation you just can't deny
Come get a taste, but can't say I won't bite
Supersonic, I'm heading out, I'm gonna
In my eyes, nirvana
Pushing for the high, my lover, I gotta
But it's fun to see you try
So hit me up! Off the map, I'mma take it, all my energy
So hit me up! Speedin' up fast, ready, target locked
So hit me up! Hit the dash, I'm upgraded and you want a piece
So hit me up! So hit me up, ah, and never stop
In a new territory, I'm on the edge of glory
Boy, just watch how I move, gimme that rush
Got no regrets in my mind, boy, it's on you this time
So hit me up! Outta luck, volume up, you got a crush
Such a cliché, your bad boy charm
Thought I'd fall right back in your arms
Wasn't enough, you needed more
Now you're begging to let you score
Surely you'll take it all in stride
Oh, I'mma be busy tonight
Goodbye, goodbye, gotta leave you dry
Always trying to play it cool, 20/20 vision on me
Just outside my field of view
Engine booming, that's my cue, catch me if you can, you better keep
Up the chase, boy, you're falling behind
Supersonic, I'm heading out, I'm gonna
But it's fun to see you try
So hit me up!
Off the map, I'mma take it, all my energy
Speedin' up fast, ready, target locked
So hit me up!
Hit the dash, I'm upgraded and you want a piece
So hit me up, ah, I never stop
In a new territory
I'm on the edge of glory
Boy, just watch how I move
Gimme that rush
Got no regrets in my mind
Boy, it's on you this time
So hit me up, outta luck, volume up
You got a crush?
Just barely wasn't enough, you should've
given me all that you got, you could've
Coming full circle, I hit a nerve, oh
Top spot getting hot, watch me run it
So hit me up!
Rev it up and make that vroom vroom, vroom vroom
When I hit you with that doom doom, doom doom
So hit me up!
If you know what's good for you, ooh ooh
Hear me now, I'm back in charge, try to copy that
Yay! Kikiriki!
Welcome to my birthday in 2025!
お誕生日です、私の！なんと、なんと！
It is my birthday! Oh my gosh, oh my gosh!
何歳になるんでしょう、この不死鳥？
How old is this phoenix turning?
It is my birthday. It is a very special occasion. It is not just my birthday...
It is also the Super Special Summer!
We will make it a super special summer today! Yes, yes!
And if you guys want, I have a hashtag up here, so please make use of it.
It is #KiaraBDay2025!
So post it all over social media! Screenshots...
...or gifs or jifs, whatever you want.
Share it to the world! Spread the Wawa love!
Thank you already in advance!
We started our first song with KIRA's "HIT ME UP".
KIRA, another banger from my good friend KIRA.
Thank you for providing the world with bangers.
I'm taking them for myself, hehe, they're mine now!
Yeah, that was fun! And did you like the little spicy dance? Hehe.
And let's take a little look at the stage! ステージもみましょうか！
And let's take a little look at the stage! Shall we look at the stage too?
Well, besides the Super Special Summer logo, we have some presents.
I wonder what's inside. And some balloons.
Maybe I'm going to pop them when I'm done here, hehe.
Yes! And then, besides that...
Today, you know why it's so special?
Well, because we're gonna have super special merch at the end. We're gonna have...
...super special outside guests! *gasp*
I've never had an outside guest before! Exciting!
And, and, and... super special song reveal? Hm...
Yeah, yeah, probably, you know me.
So please watch until the very end!
最後まで見てください！特別なサプライズいっぱいありますから、よろしくお願いします！
Please watch until the end! There are lots of special surprises, so please look forward to it!
Please listen to the next song, UNDEAD.
Hey hey hey hey, somehow feeling like there's a fight within and it's been going on so long
And I don't even know if I even want to try, that version of me, of me, of me
And those safe years of the old, transparent ghosts over my route
Those childish and painful memories have deep-seated roots
No way to deceive, way better than irony
They all see the real me of the past when looking at me now
Label I can't erase
Inner side confidence, it's almost like something is possessing me
It is wrapping tightly around
And let loose, and it's bound to self-value, used to be before
UNDEAD!
Still, a lifetime is a chain of your own
Can't be denied, always, always embrace your inner changes, hold on
Don't settle for unhappiness, don't seek for pleasure in distress
Now is the time to seize the joy and free your power
Oh, this whole, this whole world is one of, one of fantasy
Who knows what is coming up next, a monster or a snake
This is a story starting after that encounter, finally
With people of almost-dead spirits, that's happy, happy, happy, yeah
Past and future, can't change the past
Past and future, run for the future
Cutting-edge
Somehow feeling like there's nothing to be looking forward to
No hope of time can be defined, that's how I'm feeling inside
There's nothing left of you, live long enough, nothing is new
No sign of anything wonderful waiting down the line
UNDEAD! Too much knowledge results in feeling like everything is but an empty word
We have emotion, thrill is what I really want now
More than danger, still friends, and
This is the way to guidance through, rusty compliance, still
It's like I'm going under, at least I consume everything
This one or that one or whichever, and now it all just tastes the same
UNDEAD
Still alive, light, each shade of your own life
In any era, your past and your future are in this very moment
Fulfill the life you set out for, and truthfully live it
Moving on, go for that happy ending
UNDEAD
Still alive, I'm telling this to you now, so never give up
On pursuing your happiness, make it real now
For seeing all the suffering, always enduring everything
It's almost as if you're dead or alive, but which is it? Tell me!
If you are doing well, that's what matters most
Then you gotta listen very close
Keep on trying, never give up, be aware that you are alive
Drowning deep in unhappiness, or feeling that you're happy now
It's on you, it's all on you
Universe, so all embracing, all creations, peace, peace, yeah!
Past and future, can't change the past
Past and future, run for the future
Where people gather and go, you'll find no worries and foes
So you gotta live on through this life
Monsters everywhere that you can see
オールアイズピッカーン！ ライザピッカーン！
All eyes, flash! Rise up, flash!
オールアイズピッカーン！
All eyes, flash!
オールアイズピッカーン！ ライザピッカーン！
All eyes, flash! Rise up, flash!
一緒になって輝け
Let's shine together!
Ready 3, 2, 1, あー！
Ready, 3, 2, 1, ah!
サバイバルサッササッサー マッサマサッサー 頭ん中 Let's go!
Survival, step by step, completely fresh, inside my head, let's go!
もう逃げそう 無理そう デコボコな脳内 Let's go!
I'm about to run, it seems impossible, in this bumpy mind, let's go!
やっちゃえメイクアップ 勝っちゃえメイクアップ ファッションバディ
Do your makeup, win with your makeup, fashion buddy!
失敗じゃない 最低もない 最下位まで追いかけてけ
It's not a failure, there's no rock bottom, chase it all the way down to the last place!
隠された想いが あえあえ 僕らをウォッチングする
The hidden feelings, gasping, gasping, are watching us.
出会いはこれ 重なるさ 支えあえ
This is our meeting, overlapping, supporting each other.
おっとっと吸い込まれていこう
Oops, let's get sucked right in!
オールアイズピッカーン！ ライザピッカーン！
All eyes, flash! Rise up, flash!
オールアイズピッカーン！ 変えていこうよ 少女的構想
All eyes, flash! Let's change it, with a girl's vision!
オールアイズピッカーン！ ライザピッカーン！
All eyes, flash! Rise up, flash!
一緒になって輝け
Let's shine together!
Ready 3, 2, 1, あー！
Ready, 3, 2, 1, ah!
イェーイ 最高だぜ この上ないの そこのパーティー
Yeah, it's the best! Like no other, party right there!
あっという間に上がれる限界へ
Raising up to the limit in the blink of an eye!
何回だってだって晴れ 傘なんていらないや 雨
No matter how many times, it's sunny! I don't need an umbrella for the rain!
バイバイ Don't you dare 近々またやってやろうぜ
Bye bye, don't you dare! Let's do this again sometime soon!
メイデイ 助ければ問題ないね
Mayday, if you save me, there's no problem, right?
ぽつりと見る希望 明日も君と旅するでしょう 約束がちゃんと待ってるんだオッケー
A tiny hope I see, tomorrow we'll journey together again, our promise is waiting, okay!
寂しくなるわ あえあえ もうやめ 弱くない
It's gonna get lonely, gasping, gasping, stop it already, I'm not weak!
乗り越え叫べ 負けない強さを
Overcome and shout, a strength that won't lose!
おっとっと吸い込まれていこう
Oops, let's get sucked right in!
ライズアップ！ Make it 抜群 素敵に大正解
Rise up! Make it outstanding, a wonderful, perfect answer!
ライズアップ！ Make it 抜群 間違いにバイバイ 連れてって 叶えて
Rise up! Make it outstanding, bye-bye to mistakes, take me with you, make it come true!
3, 2, 1, Ready, big bang あがれ！
3, 2, 1, Ready, big bang! Rise up!
僕らのための冒険だ ゴーゴー レッツゴー！
This is an adventure for us, go go, let's go!
ハンパじゃない 燃えてる想いは上昇中
No half-measures, my burning feelings are rising!
埋もれる感傷は 君の消しゴムで消してほしい
These buried sentiments, I want you to erase them with your eraser.
期待は好きなだけ 全部僕らのため
Expect as much as you like, it's all for us!
ライズアップ！ Make it 抜群 素敵に大正解
Rise up! Make it outstanding, a wonderful, perfect answer!
ライズアップ！ Make it 抜群 間違いにバイバイ 連れてって 叶えて
Rise up! Make it outstanding, bye-bye to mistakes, take me with you, make it come true!
3, 2, 1, Ready, big bang あがれ！
3, 2, 1, Ready, big bang! Rise up!
僕らのための冒険だ ゴーゴー レッツゴー！
This is an adventure for us, go go, let's go!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
ホテルジャーニー その向こうに Hop together, Come on, rise up!
Hotel journey, beyond that, hop together, come on, rise up!
Come on, rise up! 変えていこうよ 少女的構想
Come on, rise up! Let's change it, with a girl's vision!
オールアイズピッカーン！ ライザピッカーン！
All eyes, flash! Rise up, flash!
ライズピッカーン！ ライズピッカーン！
Rise, flash! Rise, flash!
Yay!
Kiara! Kiara! Kiara! Woo!
Okay, okay, okay! Let's do self-introductions!
Even though they don't really need one. Let's start with the Senpai!
Hello! Five Generation Momosuzu Nene!
Fifthじゃなかったっけ？Fifth。
Wasn't it Fifth? Fifth.
Fifus? Fifus. / Fifus.
Fifus Generation! / Yay!
And... Kouhai!
Hello! HoloX, Iroha Kazama de gozaru!
Yay!
あまり英語入ってなかった気がする。
I feel like we didn't get much English in there.
入った！
I did!
There is not enough English!
English is so difficult! Sorry, 海外ニキ！
English is so difficult! Sorry, overseas fans!
Okay!
Nene-chi, it's been a while! 久しぶりだね。
Nene-chi, it's been a while! It's been a long time, right?
It's been a while! / It's been a while!
Two years, maybe?
Maybe two years. / Maybe two years.
...that we danced together. Long time ago!
Long time ago! 寂しかったよ！
Long time ago! I missed you!
And Iroha-chan?
Last year! Yes, last year. / Last year!
Yeah, happy happy! / Happy happy!
I feel like our colors match very well, right?
So maybe if Nene-chi is in the middle...
Look! Gradation! / Gradation!
Blonde... / Blonde.
Peach... / Peach.
Orange! / Orange!
Beautiful!
目の色は？
What about eye colors?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah! Iroha-chan's...
たしかに！いろはちゃん…
Indeed, Iroha-chan's...
Eye color is in my hair!
Yes, yes, yes! / Yes, yes, yes!
Beautiful! シナジーを感じる。
Beautiful! I can feel the synergy.
シナジー！
Synergy!
So, the song we just sang together...
...we cannot say too clearly what it was all about...
...but did you see this pose here?
Pose? / Pose?
What is this pose? I wonder.
We are holding some kind of ball here.
But it could also very well be baseball.
Baseball? / Baseball?
野球？野球かな？
Baseball? Is it baseball?
So, I want everybody to show me an original throwing pose.
Okay? Challenge! / Okay, okay!
カッコいいスロー。
A cool throw!
Yes, yes! Kawaii, anything is okay.
I start, okay? I start. / Okay.
Okay, here we go, ball throwing challenge.
3, 2, 1...
Hoi! Hoi!
Sexy! Cool! Sexy!
Okay, okay! Next, who wants to do?
Nene! Nene!
Let's go! / Let's go!
Ho!
Ball! Ball! Ball!
Very cute! Very cute!
Iroha-chan?
拙者もそういうの欲しい。
I want to do something cool like that too!
I'll go! / Go!
Whoa, whoa, whoa...
構えからの…
Stance, and...
斬り！
Slash!
ナイス斬り！
Nice slash!
またつまらぬものを斬ってしまったでござる。
"Once again, I have cut a worthless object."
Very nice, very nice!
The viewers and audience maybe can tell us which one was best.
But for now, because I still have many more guests...
...and many more songs, I have to take this jacket off...
...so please!
お着替えします。
I'll change clothes.
隠さなきゃ！
We have to hide her!
キアラちゃん隠せ！
Hide Kiara-chan!
見ないで見ないで。
Don't look, everyone!
Okay!
Tada! / Cute!
Thank you! Thank you!
可愛い！
Cute!
もうバイバイの時間ですね。
It's already time to say goodbye.
No... / But thank you!
楽しかった！
It was fun!
またやりましょう！
Let's do it again!
次の曲も頑張ってね！
Good luck with the next song too!
頑張って！
Good luck!
Bye bye! / Bye bye!
Yeah! / Uh-huh.
Get-get-get-get a little attention
I bet you don't know me yet
君の奥底まで 穿つ目線で
Piercing all the way to your depths with my gaze
溢れる余韻 極まる展開
Overflowing resonance, the ultimate development
Catalyst, I know once I go, put your hands up
感情の最中に 降臨した女神
A goddess descended in the midst of emotion
I freeze it up, got it ice cold on my body
You wanna know but you don't, 侵攻させていく脳
You wanna know but you don't, taking over your brain
I'm a go, I'm-ma show, show, show, show, show
Can't snap, get back my fantasy
Now you see...
星空を灯すマント達と共に
Together with the starry-sky-lighting cloaks...
In a deep breath within my universe, come find me now
Hear the voice that's calling out
まだ見ぬ世界の真髄を見せてあげるから baby, focus now
Because I'll show you the essence of the world you've yet to see, baby, focus now
Calm down, let me focus
Under my spell, like hypnosis
So don't get too close when I...
Come, come, come, coming through
You wanna roll with me?
We're taking them down, yeah
I tell you what to do, I've got nothing to prove
Cold when I move, when I move, when I focus
I tell you what to do, known as my bulletproof
Cold when I do what I do, what I do when I focus
Oh me, back at my best, I finesse with this nanori
秘かにすべてを secret
Secretly keeping everything a secret
Glistening cool, my attitude
Target in my sight, lock in, ready to shoot, like...
Mayday, this is an emergency
Working under pressure, baby, I can do this in my sleep
夜の理だって書き換えてしまうような夏の...
Like rewriting the very laws of the night, in this summer...
When I go, when I go, when I go, I'm gonna shine, shine, shine, shine
Won't stop, gotta make my fantasy
Now you see...
銀河を音色は外で attraction に
With the galaxy outside, the melody becomes an attraction
Deep breath within my universe, come find me now
Clear my mind of all of this doubt
まだ見ぬ世界の真髄 この目で見たいから baby, focus now
Because I want to see the essence of the world yet unseen with my own eyes, baby, focus now
Calm down, let me focus
Under my spell, like hypnosis
So don't get too close when I...
Come, come, come, coming through
You wanna roll with me?
We're taking them down, yes
I tell you what to do, I've got nothing to prove
Cold when I move, when I move, when I focus
I tell you what to do, notes are my bulletproof
Cold when I do what I do, what I do when I focus
Oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh
Tada no ko, but don't break my focus
Just a girl, but don't break my focus
Oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh
Wanna try and play catch up? Follow my mind
I'ma get it, talk about it loud, can't get rid of me now
I'm gonna get it, talk about it loud, can't get rid of me now
Ue to shimo ni so crown, put my feet on the ground
Up and down, so crown, put my feet on the ground
Makasareteku, S, piece of cake, no stress
Leave it to me, S-class, piece of cake, no stress
Ima chuu wo miryou shite, what's next? Take a guess
Charming the air now, what's next? Take a guess
Yes, I tell you what to do, I've got nothing to prove
Cold when I move, when I move, when I focus
I tell you what to do, notes are my bulletproof
Cold when I do what I do, what I do when I focus
Oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh
Tada no ko, but don't break my focus
Just a girl, but don't break my focus
Oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh
Wanna try and play catch up? Follow my mind
Focus
So bae, おおせのままに
So bae, as you command
願うは自己
What I wish for is my ego
一世一代
Once in a lifetime
沙汰に落とす慈悲も躊躇
The mercy cast into judgment, even hesitation...
そんじゃ負け犬、泥縄なんてないや
Then, you loser, no room for belated prep
幕開けるわ
The curtain will rise
勝ちにして
Turn it into a win
ラッキー？ 何、どっちも無理
Lucky? What, both are impossible
違う 違う
No, no!
ひっくり返すタッグな自分、指導、異論、NO
Inverting the tag-team of myself, coaching, objections, NO
余裕で振り切ってへっちゃら Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Shaking it off with ease, piece of cake, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
即お届け
Delivered immediately
即お寝ね
Going to sleep immediately
かっさらうのは私だ
The one who will snatch it away is me
Say "mou ii" 勝ったなら兵糧攻め
Say "enough"—if we win, we starve them out
Playboy 避けて don't get in my way
Playboy, move aside, don't get in my way
じゃあね 黙って
See ya, shut your mouth
One, two, three / One, two, three / One, two, three
Sit down, sit down
刃物振り回し気味ね 手ぇ挙げてな
Seems you're brandishing a blade, put your hands up
脳を犯した既成しがらみ 近づくのちいさ
Brain-damaged established bonds, we know of your approach
あぁ 離れないでしょ
Ah, you won't leave, right?
Show, show, show, say goodbye
あっちこっち そっちこっち enough, enough, enough
Here, there, this way, that way, enough, enough, enough
みっともない君を
You, looking so pathetic
病み 病み 病みや
Sick, sick, so sick of you
空回り、そう
Running in circles, indeed
でもまだ止めないで
But don't stop just yet
あの窓、そう
That window, indeed
超え超えされどされど逃げ... oneway
Cross it, cross it, but even so, escape is a... one-way
あんたここまで
You're only up to here
後ろ姿だけ見とけ
Just keep staring at my back
勝ちにして
Turn it into a win
ラッキー？ 何、どっちも無理
Lucky? What, both are impossible
違う 違う
No, no!
ひっくり返すタッグな自分、指導、異論、NO
Inverting the tag-team of myself, coaching, objections, NO
余裕で振り切ってへっちゃら Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Shaking it off with ease, piece of cake, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
即お届け
Delivered immediately
即お寝ね
Going to sleep immediately
かっさらうのは私だ
The one who will snatch it away is me
Say "mou ii" 勝ったなら兵糧攻め
Say "enough"—if we win, we starve them out
Playboy 避けて don't get in my way
Playboy, move aside, don't get in my way
じゃあね 黙って
See ya, shut your mouth
ねえ待って 待って
Hey, wait, wait!
1 2 3, 1 2 3, 1 2 3, Sit down, sit down.
1 2 3, 1 2 3, 1 2 3
まさかのバイバイ
An unexpected goodbye!
1 2 3, 1 2 3, 1 2 3, Sit down, sit down.
Sit down, sit down.
I like it, I like it, ah
I like it, I like it
I like them tall, He's my perfect 規格外
I like them tall, He's my perfect misfit
必要なのはただ numbers and code
All that's needed are just numbers and code
甘くエディット 素敵な創り話
Sweetly edited, a wonderful made-up story
いこう Let them click, link, make it snap, clap
Let's go! Let them click, link, make it snap, clap
教えてあげるよ イニシエトリック
I'll teach you an ancient trick
一千五百超えると天国も売却
Once it exceeds 1,500, even heaven is sold off
Link, make it snap, clap
Oh, my lord 疲れ果てても信じたくない
Oh, my lord, even if I'm exhausted, I don't want to believe it
Always an ace 僕のためだけトイ
Always an ace, a toy just for me
愛されたい覚悟は？ 甘甘、や甘甘
Are you prepared to be loved? Sweet sweet, oh sweet sweet
Puzzled pieces of love 今 完璧にフィットする fake heart, fake heart
Puzzled pieces of love, now perfectly fitting fake heart, fake heart
Puzzled pieces of love もっと僕の思い通りに Start it up and complete
Puzzled pieces of love, even more just the way I want it, start it up and complete
Fake, fake, fake heart
(I like it, I like it!)
Fake, fake,全部バラバラ
Fake, fake, everything is falling apart
何度もリスタート Fake, fake is my target
Starting over again and again, fake, fake is my target
ちょっと待てよ パッと見てよ
Wait a minute, take a quick look
やり合い世界変えて行きましょう
Let's compete and change the world
クック確率 誰でも神になる
Click probability, anyone can become a god
リセットするカウントダウン 3, 2, 1
Resetting countdown 3, 2, 1
ようこそ僕の playground 未来の天地開闢
Welcome to my playground, the creation of the future heaven and earth
100%満足 約束しますから
Because I promise 100% satisfaction
有機的とか時代遅れ ついてきなさもなくば
Organic is so outdated, keep up or else...
ラブ聞くの？ お上手、残念。 執着した君の...
Listen to love? Well done, too bad. You who became obsessed...
Oh, my lord 疲れ果てても信じたくない
Oh, my lord, even if I'm exhausted, I don't want to believe it
Always an ace 僕のためだけトイ
Always an ace, a toy just for me
愛されたい覚悟は？ 甘甘、や甘甘
Are you prepared to be loved? Sweet sweet, oh sweet sweet
Puzzled pieces of love 今 完璧にフィットする fake heart, fake heart
Puzzled pieces of love, now perfectly fitting fake heart, fake heart
Puzzled pieces of love もっと僕の思い通りに Start it up and complete
Puzzled pieces of love, even more just the way I want it, start it up and complete
Fake, fake, fake heart
(I like it, I like it!)
Fake, fake,全部バラバラ
Fake, fake, everything is falling apart
何度もリスタート Fake, fake is my target
Starting over again and again, fake, fake is my target
夢か現実か どっちでもいい
Is it a dream or reality? Either way is fine
理想に生きたい Oh, yeah
I want to live in the ideal, oh yeah
強引にプログラム 融解までいそごう
Forcibly program it, let's hurry until fusion
この命は短し
This life is short
Perfect!
Again!
何が悪いわけ？
What's so wrong with it?
Puzzled pieces of love 今 完璧にフィットする fake heart, fake heart
Puzzled pieces of love, now perfectly fitting fake heart, fake heart
Puzzled pieces of love もっと僕の思い通りに Start it up and complete
Puzzled pieces of love, even more just the way I want it, start it up and complete
Follow, follow, I like it, I like it, 液晶閉じるフィクション
Follow, follow, I like it, I like it, fiction that closes the LCD screen
Follow, follow, I like it, I like it, 迷い込む宇宙
Follow, follow, I like it, I like it, getting lost in space
Follow, follow, I like it, I like it, ハマったらもう最期
Follow, follow, I like it, I like it, once you fall in, it's the end
Follow, follow, I like it, I like it, 楽しんで
Follow, follow, I like it, I like it, enjoy it!
Whoa oh oh...
My heart starts skipping a beat
気取りたいシチュエーション
A situation where I want to look cool
様変わりだす Expression time
The changing expression time
全然悪くない Imagination
Not a bad imagination at all
視界の霧は晴れわたって
The fog in my vision clears up
悲しみに別れを告げる
Bidding farewell to sadness
水際、祭りは満ち足りて リズム
By the water's edge, the festival is fulfilled, rhythm...
ライク・ア... ライク・ア・バタフライ
Like a... Like a butterfly
どれだけうまく見せようとしても
No matter how well I try to show off
君がいなければ
If you are not here
何の意味もない
It has no meaning at all
かすり傷すらつかない幻想
An illusion without even a scratch
針の落ちないレコードさ
Like a record whose needle won't drop
冷たい 止め度ない 追い風 背にして
With a cold, endless tailwind at my back
Come on, let's roll
そっと吹き荒れる 向かい風にも心
Gently blowing, even in the headwind, my heart...
なびかせて
Letting it sway
飛び乗って To the future
Jump on, to the future
フライングしたって オールライト リスタートライン
Even with a false start, it's alright, restart line
ときめいてしまえば
If your heart starts beating fast
瞬く間に広がる解放区
The liberated zone spreads in the blink of an eye
一つ一つ 全てがドラマ
Each and every thing is a drama
待ちわびたデイブレイク リスタートライン
The long-awaited daybreak, restart line
変わり変わる色づくパノラマ
The ever-changing, colorful panorama
満ち溢れる フィーリングラデーション
An overflowing feeling gradation
始まりの その時が来た
The time for the beginning has come
Nothing is impossible
まやかし ごまかし きりがない世界
Deceptions and illusions, in this endless world
この先はまだ 誰も知らない世界
The path ahead is a world nobody knows yet
傍観してるだけじゃ 味気ない
Just standing by and watching is tasteless
リアルタイムで 通じ合って
Connecting with each other in real-time
振り切るだけのモーション
A motion just to break through
お決まりのルールなら I don't mind
I don't mind the established rules
大胆不敵なシチュエーション
A daring and fearless situation
いけるところまで行ってみたい目標
I want to go as far as I can
選択肢にない 描く彼方のウェイ保存
An unlisted path toward the beyond we paint
共に声を鳴らせ
Let's make our voices ring out together
素肌を貫くような まっすぐな痛みが
A piercing, straight-on pain against the skin
灯っても
Even if it lights up
この道が立ち塞がっても<
Even if this road blocks our way
Keep on running to the end
飛び乗って To the future
Jump on, to the future
フライングしたって オールライト リスタートライン
Even with a false start, it's alright, restart line
ときめいてしまえば
If your heart starts beating fast
瞬く間に広がる解放区
The liberated zone spreads in the blink of an eye
一つ一つ 全てがドラマ
Each and every thing is a drama
待ちわびたデイブレイク リスタートライン
The long-awaited daybreak, restart line
変わり変わる色づくパノラマ
The ever-changing, colorful panorama
満ち溢れる フィーリングラデーション
An overflowing feeling gradation
研ぎ澄ませヒューマニティ
Sharpen your humanity
恐れるものはない リスタートライン
There is nothing to fear, restart line
きれいなサヨナラが
A beautiful goodbye
透明な明日を 照らしだすよ
Will illuminate a transparent tomorrow
リスタートライン
Restart line
キアラ先輩！
Kiara-senpai!
ハッピーバースデー！
Happy birthday!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
ありがとう！ ありがとう！
Thank you! Thank you so much!
Thank you! Thank you! Well, you wished me a happy birthday...
Thank you, thank you! Well, you've wished me happy birthday...
But since we went to Austria together...
Can you say it in German?
Happy birthday? / Yes!
Sure, sure!
Okay, I'll teach you. I'll teach you.
You don't know, right? / I don't know, sorry!
教えてもらえるんだ、よかった！ / Yeah, yeah.
We get to be taught! Thank goodness! / Yeah, yeah.
It's Alles Gute... / Alles Gute?
Gute. / Gute?
Yes, Alles Gute. / Alles Gute?
zum... / zum?
Geburtstag. / Geburtstag!
Oh! Okay, okay!
せーの！
Ready, go!
Alles Gute zum Geburtstag!
Yeah! Yay!
もう半分オーストリア人になった！
You're already half-Austrian now!
Yeah, thank you! ズパダケ！
Yeah, thank you! Super danke!
ズパダケ！ ズパダケ！
Super danke! Super danke!
Okay, 自己紹介 in English! / Okay!
Okay, self-introduction in English! / Okay!
誰から？ りりか？
Who's first? Ririka?
Hi! Hello everyone!
Kawaii positive energian! I'm Ririka Ichijou...
from Hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS! Nice to meet you!
Next!
Hello everyone!
はーい！えー、儒烏風亭らでんfromホロライブデバイスReGLOSSでーす！イェーイ！
Hi! I'm Juufuutei Raden from Hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS! Yay!
ペラペラ、ペラペラ！
Bla bla bla!
Okay, everyone! We danced your song together!
Yeah! Thank you! Thank you! I'm so happy!
Feeling Gradation!
I'm feeling very happy to be able to dance this song because it's so cool! めっちゃカッコいい曲！
I'm feeling very happy to be able to dance this song because it's so cool! A super cool song!
How was it to dance with like a non-ReGLOSS member?
It's actually first time to dance together, uh, who is not ReGLOSS member, so...
It's actually our first time dancing together with someone who is not a ReGLOSS member, so...
I was a little bit nervous, but finally, we can do it! Yay! Happy!
I was a little bit nervous, but finally, we can do it! Yay! So happy!
I think, you know, I chose the white version of this outfit because I thought we look so good together! Fits all of us! Yay!
I think, you know, I chose the white version of this outfit because I thought we look so good together! It fits all of us! Yay!
So, because we look so good together, let's take a cute picture, okay?
Okay, okay! Strike a pose!
I will go like here... No, closer, closer, closer! Okay!
I will go right here... No, closer, closer, closer! Okay!
Yeah! Screenshot! Screenshot! Yatta!
Yeah! Screenshot! Screenshot! We did it!
Thank you, thank you! I had so much fun! 握手！ Me too! Super danke!
Thank you, thank you! I had so much fun! Handshake! Me too! Super danke!
じゃあ、えー、フィーリング・グラデーションをリグロスのこの可愛いお二人と一緒に踊りましたけども...
Well, we just danced 'Feeling Gradation' with these two cute ReGLOSS members, but...
I have even more guests coming, and even more songs coming! And for that, I will go to the center stage!
Oh, Senpai! Okay, bye bye! Bye bye! See you! スパダケ！スパダケ！がんばれ、がんばれー！
Oh, Senpai! Okay, bye-bye! Bye-bye! See you! Super danke! Super danke! Do your best!
帰ろう！だらんだらん...
Let's head back!
出会えや 出会え 孤独も散らして
Come on out, gather, and scatter the loneliness
祝い合え 宴 大胆な幕開け
Celebrate together, feast, a bold beginning
積もる無い くだらない 話です、です、です、あれ？
Just catching up with idle chatter... wait, what?
ありきなりらりらり毎日に ちょっと抜け駆け
Slipping away slightly from the same old, ordinary days
欲しがってんのは最新 カットのジョーダン
What you're wanting is the latest high-cut Jordans
そんでもって無限大級の頂上
And with that, we're at the peak of infinite scale
ショートカットでちょっとジャンプ 今夜も一等駆け抜ける
A little jump with a shortcut, running through in first place tonight as well
愛してバースデー！
Love me, happy birthday!
1 2 3 ときめきに Never give up
1, 2, 3, never give up on this excitement
連れ出して 連れ出して その歌で
Take me away, take me away with that song
燦々僕らが 出会えば
When we, shining brilliantly, meet...
特別映えるワンシーン
...it creates a truly special scene
見逃せない夜は
This unmissable night is...
永遠！
Eternal!
同調ターゲット 足元 進む先を教えて
Synchronize with the target, show me where my feet are heading
未知の道へ ロックバックバックバック 抜け抜け
To the unknown road, lock back back back, sneak away
なるようになっていくだけ いつもほら航海中
Just letting things take their course, look, we're always on a voyage
失敗談も自己流のオーダーメイド中
Even our failures are custom-made in our own style
欠けてるどこかが あたしたちのオリジナリティ
The parts of us that are lacking are what make up our originality
燦々涙を流した
The brilliant tears we shed...
その分だけ星になれ 煌めいて
...will become stars and shine all the brighter
不安を風に溶かして
Dissolving our anxiety into the wind
あの日かけたマジックが今だ解けない
The magic cast on that day still won't fade
永遠！
Eternal!
一息で壊した ノームの踊り場
Destroyed in a single breath, the gnome's dance floor
与えられた答えなんてきっと
The answers we were given are surely...
勝てん甲斐ないベイビー 障壁リミット
Our barriers and limits are gone, baby
It's now or never あたしの革命は絶対
It's now or never, my revolution is absolute
一、十、百、千、万！ 飛ばしな！
One, ten, hundred, thousand, ten thousand! Let's fly!
Don't worry,僕たちは Never give up
Don't worry, we will never give up
躍らせて 躍らせて その歌で
Make us dance, make us dance with that song
逢う、逢う、朝を見つけた
Meeting again and again, we found the morning sun
また拓き 色づく新世界 愛してバースデー！
Opening once more, painting a new world! Love me, happy birthday!
永遠！
Eternal!
絡みつくこの響きは変わらずに
This echoing sound that entangles us will never change
言う
...and say...
あいた穴をここから君に注ぐ
From here, filling the hole that opened up for you
愛しているよ ずっと Never give up！
I will love you forever, never give up!
永遠！
Eternal!
Hey hey baby, 言おうか？
Hey hey baby, shall we say it?
吸い上げな
Suck it up!
愛してバースデー！
Love me, happy birthday!
Let me know
どこで
Where...
どんな
and what kind of...
景色
scenery...
見てる？
are you looking at?
君に
To you,
続け I'll do anything, anywhere
I'll keep on... I'll do anything, anywhere
DISTANCE
[Song: DISTANCE]
この地図の指し示す方へ
To where this map points,
君の足取りたどりながら
following in your footsteps.
憧れを力に変えて
Turning my longing into strength,
Rock my world, baby
あれからどれくらい
Since then, how much
君に追いつけただろう
have I caught up with you?
いつでも前を行くその背中を
I've kept watching your back
見つめ続けてきた
as you always lead the way.
遠い道のり
The long journey...
超えてゆくたびに
every time I overcome it,
本当の強さの
the meaning of true...
意味を知るから
strength becomes clear to me.
すべてを投げ出したとしたとしてもまだ
Even if I were to throw everything away...
君との距離感つめ切れなくて
...I still can't close the distance with you.
あの日々 あの時 思い起こせば
If I look back at those days, at those times,
この想いをとどけ
I want to send this feeling to you!
どこで
Where...
どんな
and what kind of...
景色
scenery...
見てる？
are you looking at?
君に
To you,
続け I'll do anything, anywhere
I'll keep on... I'll do anything, anywhere
いつかは誰かが私の",s:
Someday, someone might
背中を追うようになるかも
follow in my footsteps too.
それでもペースは落とさずに
Even so, without slowing my pace,
Run to you, baby
I'll run to you, baby!
振り返らずにゴールを
Without looking back,
目指し走ってゆく
I'll run aiming for the goal.
いつも自分が拓いた
Always believing in
道の上にいることだけ信じて
the path that I have carved.
たとえ何度も
Even if I feel...
壁を感じても
...walls blocking me time and again,
茨の道を
I'll overcome...
乗り越えてみせる
...this thorny path and show you!
すべてを投げ出したとしたとしてもまだ
Even if I were to throw everything away...
君との距離感つめ切れなくて
...I still can't close the distance with you.
あの日々 あの時 思い起こせば
If I look back at those days, at those times,
この想いをとどけ
I want to send this feeling to you!
どこで
Where...
どんな
and what kind of...
景色
scenery...
見てる？
are you looking at?
君に
To you,
続け I'll do anything, anywhere
I'll keep on... I'll do anything, anywhere
また君と会える日を信じて
Believing in the day I can meet you again,
受け止めた想いを未来へと
these feelings I've gathered...
届けるのさ
...I'll deliver them to the future!
すべてを投げ出したとしたとしてもまだ
Even if I were to throw everything away...
君との距離感つめ切れなくて
...I still can't close the distance with you.
あの日々 あの時 思い起こせば
If I look back at those days, at those times,,
この想いをとどけ
I want to send this feeling to you!
どこで
Where...
どんな
and what kind of......
景色
scenery...
見てる？
are you looking at?
君に
To you,
続け I'll do anything, anywhere
I'll keep on... I'll do anything, anywhere
Let me know
レディーマーメイド
[Song: Lady Mermaid]
One, for the one
乾いた海岸線
The dry coastline,
飛ばした奴らが集まる
where those who sped along gather.
あの店 2人のステージ
That place is a stage for the two of us.
双子みたいにバッチリ まつげは今日も
Like twins, our eyelashes are perfect today too,
潮風受け止めているわ
catching the salty sea breeze.
2人が踊りだしたらほら
See, once the two of us start to dance,
誰にも負けないわ Step, baby
we won't lose to anyone, step baby!
Let's dance tonight!
海岸通りの噂　アタシたちのものなの
The rumors on the coastal highway belong to us.
虜にするわ　逃がさない
We'll captivate you, we won't let you escape.
Come on, come on, come on, my darling!
渚に踊る
Dancing on the shoreline,
キミとアタシは
you and I,
今も昔も
now and forever,
レディーマーメイド Hey Boy Hoo!
Lady Mermaids! Hey boy, woo!
恋も車も
Both love and cars
夏は渋滞さ
experience traffic jams in the summer.
人魚の恋はね
A mermaid's love is,
儚いものなの
a fleeting thing, you see.
泣いて笑ったね End of the Summer
We cried and laughed, didn't we? End of the summer.
One for the one
Ah...
誰も彼も街の景色は変わってゆくさ
Everyone and everything, the city scenery keeps on changing.
二人は変わらないけど
Though the two of us remain unchanged.
Ah...
コンクリートに消えて無くなる砂浜
The sandy beach that disappears into the concrete...
なんだか切なくなるね
Somehow, it makes me feel a bit sad.
キミが街を飛び出してさ
When you dashed out of the city,
夢と、ともに暮らした City My Life My Way
and lived with your dreams in the city, my life my way.
都会の匂い憧れ
Longing for the scent of the city,
キミがいなくなったの
you were gone.
一人の海は広すぎて
The ocean all by myself is much too vast.
Get back, get back, get back, my friend!
海辺の街で
In the seaside town,
二人でひとつ
the two of us were one,
ずっと前から
for a very long time,
一緒さ Hey Girl Hoo!
we've been together! Hey girl, woo!
秋が来たなら
If autumn comes,
潮が引くように
just like the ebbing tide,
誰も彼も車も
everyone and every car
いなくなるかね
will fade away, won't they?
海岸通りを飛ばそうぜ
Let's speed down the coastal highway!
渚に踊る
Dancing on the shoreline,
キミとアタシは
you and I,
今も昔も
now and forever,
レディーマーメイド Hey Boy Hoo!
Lady Mermaids! Hey boy, woo!
恋も車も
Both love and cars
夏は渋滞さ
experience traffic jams in the summer.
一夏の夢と
With a single summer's dream,
駆け抜けてみても
even if we try to outrun it,
二人で泣いてた End of the Summer
we were crying together. End of the summer.
海辺の街で
In the seaside town,
二人でひとつ
the two of us were one,
ずっと前から
for a very long time,
一緒さ Hey Girl Hoo!
we've been together! Hey girl, woo!
冬の潮風
The winter sea breeze
頬を突き刺すわ
pierces through our cheeks.
季節外れのレディーマーメイド
Off-season Lady Mermaids...
泣いて笑ったね End of the Summer
We cried and laughed, didn't we? End of the summer.
海岸通りを飛ばそうぜ
Let's speed down the coastal highway!
One for the one
Woo! Yeah! We did it! We did it!
Okay! Let's start right ahead with our introductions!
Hello, everybody! My name is Mint Fantome. I am a ghost maid VTuber.
I am not a part of Hololive, but I am a big fan of Ms. Takanashi Kiara!
Yeah!
It is our first ever 3D appearance together. (Together.)
And we sang a beautiful song that I think means a lot to both of us. (To both of us.)
What's it called? It was... Lady Mermaid.
From, uh, some two beautiful ladies from Hello! Project.
Suzuki Airi and Sugaya Risako, who, by now, you guys should really remember those names.
...of the Easter live that I had, okay?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, so it's Holo project all over again.
We had a lot of fun with that, right?
We did!
Practicing together.
Shaking the booty!
When we were doing practice every time, we would like, do this part...
...we would stare at each other.
So fun, yeah.
I'm so happy that we're together.
And you're here!
I know!
It's like... honestly, really does feel like this is a different timeline.
Somehow, you ended up here!
Yeah!
Maybe.
Is this kind of fun to like... today I'm roleplaying.
A little bit!
I wonder which generation you're from if you're roleplaying.
And then, I also got to see the big wall of the signatures and everything.
Yeah, it's been really exciting being here at the Hololive Studio, so...
...thank you everybody, thank you Kiara, thank you for having me!
Yeah, it's my first time having an external guest, so that's exciting!
Really?
Yeah.
Yeah, I've been like, kind of trying to get something going for a while, but then it never worked out.
But now finally, you're ready! Like I was going to honestly invite you earlier, but you know, it took you a while to...
...become this.
I feel too... I feel too honored for this. I feel like I'm too small for this position.
I feel like...
Okay.
So anyway...
This was a special time but, so, fact is, fact of the matter is, you are a maid...
...yes...
...and you have to like kind of pay for this exposure I've given you.
So, I would like you to clean the stage please, 'cause there's dirt, dirt, dirt, dirt!
Get rid of it!
Where did this come from?
You're a maid, right? Clean it up!
I have no materials. I'll just use my hands.
Why is it not going away?
You're so bad at this!
I'm sorry, Tenchou.
Let me kiss your feet.
You better! All KFP are crying right now.
Get to work!
It's not going away!
Mamma mia, oh my god, can you not do anything right?
I'm sorry, Tenchou. Please forgive me, don't kick me out!
No, I am not forgiving you, I will show you how it's done. Okay?
Okay!
You know what? I am going to get you!
I am going to catch you!
What are you doing? You're stealing! You're stealing!
I got to catch you!
We're like diamonds in starlight
Turn it up to the top, let's get it started
Go non-stop, bust through the door, we don't knock
Cause they never got us, like we never care about what they said
Tear up the place like it's our own, we're wilder than a cyclone
And leave it on a high note
And it's just like magic, lighting up the sky
When we're together, we don't have to try
If you want to join, then this is your invite
Show what you got, come on, don't be shy
We, we are breaking through borders
Free, like the clouds are beneath us, oh we
We're like diamonds in starlight, we're shining in dark night
Cause we are the highlight
We, we're just living this moment
Free, on this path that we've chosen, oh we
We're like diamonds in starlight, we're shining in the dark night
Cause we are the highlight
Don't turn it down, full of doubts, it's time to make it pop
Make us believe, lose control, let's keep the fun
Move our body, getting down like we do
Move our body, like a party with me, girl!
And it's just like magic, lighting up the sky
When we're together, we don't have to try
If you want to join, then this is your invite
Show what you got, come on, don't be shy
We, we are breaking through borders
Free, like the clouds are beneath us, oh we
We're like diamonds in starlight, we're shining in dark night
Cause we are the highlight
We, we're just living this moment
Free...
...on this path that we've chosen.
Oh, we are...
We're like diamonds in starlight,
We shine in the dark night,
Cause we are the highlight!
Don't lose your dream, make it reality, baby.
Don't lose your dream, make it...
Now everybody let me hear you say!
Don't lose your dream, go and make history, baby.
Don't lose your dream...
We...
We are breaking through borders.
Free...
Like nobody can stop us,
Oh, we are...
Diamonds in starlight,
Cause you know that we are...
We are breaking through borders.
Free...
Like the clouds are beneath us,
Oh, we are...
We're like diamonds in starlight,
We shine in the dark night,
Cause we are the highlight!
We...
We're just burning this moment.
Free...
On this path that we've chosen.
Oh, we are...
We're like diamonds in starlight,
We shine in the dark night,
Cause we are the highlight!
Highlight, highlight, highlight, highlight!
Highlight, highlight, highlight! Yay!
That was another banger from Kiara, and...
...I did it with all my beloved ID girls!
I love you, I love you ID girls, I love you so much!
Yes! So, after this wonderful banger,
as you may have noticed if you look at the time,
it might be time to end soon.
And therefore, I will introduce some merchandise to you guys!
It's birthday merchandise time!
ではでは、誕生日記念のグッズ出るので、紹介したいと思います！
So, some birthday merchandise will be released, and I'd like to introduce them!
どうぞ！見ていきましょう！Let's check it out!
Here they are! Let's check them out! Let's check it out!
That is the overview, and...
...now let me show you all of them in detail.
First of all, the tapestry! じゃじゃん！
First of all, the tapestry! Ta-da!
As you can tell, I am in a wedding dress!
なんと！なんと！私、なんか、可愛い服着てますね！
Wow! Look at that! I'm wearing a really cute outfit!
あー、恥ずかしい！
Ah, how embarrassing!
Yeah, um, it's about time, right? I don't know.
It's a beautiful tapestry. I haven't done a tapestry in a while, so I thought you guys deserved one.
And next, with the same beautiful face,
and a different expression perhaps, it will be a little badge.
So if you are a badge collector, now is the time.
If you have an ita-bag or something to fill up, now's the time to get yourself a wawa badge,
a Wawawaifu badge.
Oh, and by the way, the illustration is by DOTORI!
Thank you so much, it's so beautiful, it looks so cute!
バッジ集めてる人もぜひ今回、
For those of you who collect badges,
どうぞいっぱい買ってください。ありがとうございます！
please go ahead and buy a bunch this time. Thank you so much!
And next up is the lamp! Yeah!
The title is: You Light Up My Life Lamp.
Because it's a chicken, it's a KFP chicken!
はい、私の人生を照らしてくれるのがあなたたちなので、
Yes, since you guys are the ones who light up my life,
その姿を通したランプでございます！
this lamp is modeled after that form!
And next we have the Anger Management Frog Ball!
Froggy Wawa!
Perfect, right? You want to squeeze it, squish her head, don't you? Me too!
おこ、おこ、おこマネジメント、カエルボールでございます。
It's the Anger... Anger Management Frog Ball.
フロギーワワの顔ついてるボールです。
It's a ball with Froggy Wawa's face on it.
とてもキュートですけど、
It's very cute, but...
なんかね、押したいんだよね！
...you kind of want to squish it, don't you?!
And next we have a situational voice! Yes!
It is matching with the tapestry, actually.
So, it fits it, you know,
like this whole like honeymoon wedding situation.
Normally, I don't really go that hard on the romance
in my voice packs, since it's embarrassing,
but I tried this time! Just this once! 今回...
but I tried this time! Just this once! This time...
だけ
Only...
え ちょっと恥ずかしい ロマンチックなシチュエーションです
It's a slightly embarrassing, romantic situation.
え タペストリーに合わせてます
It matches the tapestry.
日本語もあります よかったらどうぞ！
There is also a Japanese version, so please check it out!
きゃん！
Kyah!
And for the full set, if you want the full set,
you will get a postcard extra,
and a limited amount will be signed by me with my hand,
and the rest will be stamped.
数量限定版は私のサインが入るポストカードが特典になっています
The limited-quantity version includes a postcard signed by me as a bonus.
で、その他はスタンプです。
And the rest will have a stamp.
And! And another special bonus if you get the full set...
is a hololive card! Special hololive card! Yeah!
This can be used in the hololive official card game!
But you have to purchase the full set through the official website.
GeekJack or any others are not possible.
And if you want to learn how to play, please check out the hololive official card game website! Yeah!
タレントプレミアムグッズのフルセット特典として、もう一つ追加、このカードがついてきます！
As a full set bonus for the talent premium goods, one more bonus, this card is included!
はい、ちゃんとホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームで使用できます！やった！
Yes, you can actually use it in the hololive official card game! Yay!
えーと、カードの詳細はホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームの公式ホームページにて確認してください。
Um, please check the official website of the hololive official card game for details on the card.
イェイイェイ、ナイス！特典が二つ！
Yeah yeah, nice! Two bonuses!
And next, after all this merch announcement,
let me just tell you that the merch... you can get it...
after the next song.
Because the next song will be my next original song!
And it's called TASTY! Ta-dan!
Yes! TASTY is the name of my next original song,
and it will start being released on all streaming services
at midnight your time. Whatever your timezone is, it will be up on midnight.
But the music video will come up right after this. We will raid into it, unless it doesn't work.
But we'll raid into it, and you will see the music video.
And after the music video, the merch will be available
at the 10-minute mark of whatever hour you are in. Okay?
私の新曲です！やったー！
It's my new song! Yay!
TASTYでございます！この後披露します。この後MVも公開されます！
It is TASTY! I'll perform it right after this, and the MV will be released too!
で、その後にグッズも出ます！よろしくお願いします！
And after that, the merch will be released! Thank you so much!
So with that, it is finally time
for the last song of my birthday live,
and my new original song.
So please listen to TASTY.
Ah, ah, ah, ah...
Tasty, tasty, tasty...
Tongue tied, oh you don't gotta hide it
Obvious I get you excited
Don't want perfume on my skin, just need you, yeah
Sugary thoughts, nah I don't mind it
Confection affection, it feels right
Flavor makes you go out of control
No beggin' needed, just take a bite
Lemme show you what I can take, make ache
I'll make you feel like you're alive
Alive, alive, feel your heartbeat
Honey drippin', you see what we've done tonight
Just a little taste of me
Sweet like sugar, rotten down to the core
Savor every little taste, give you more
Flavored hard candy, addictive so sweet
You got me like that, that, that, that
T-taste me, gettin' every drop
You know you like it a lot
You know I'm taste, taste, taste, taste
Taste me, tell me what do you want
I'll be your la-lollipop, you know I'm taste...
Baby, look at my picture, know you wanna be my mister, mister
I can be a little bitter, switch up, whimper, worship me like I'm scripture
This sickly sweet, candied love
Makes you want more, mm wow, are you satisfied now?
Hear you say, you want me
Can't stop the way your eyes wander, oh
So dolce...
Lemme show you what I can make, take ache
I'll make you feel like you're alive
Alive, alive, feel your heartbeat
Honey drippin', you see what we've done tonight
Just a little taste of me
Sweet like sugar, rotten down to the core
Savor every little taste, give you more
Flavored hard candy, addictive so sweet
You got me like that, that, that, that
That that that that
Ooh
Sweet aroma
Got us both actin' up tonight
tonight
Ooh
Sugar coma
Fall into me you want it
no
Baby, I'm sweet for you
I'm a keep it tasty, tasty
Know you like this taste, taste, taste
T-taste me
Gettin' every drop
You know you like it a lot
You know I'm taste, taste, taste, taste
Taste me
Tell me what do you want
I'll be your la-lollipop
You know I'm taste, taste, taste, taste
So sweet, not enough of me
Drippin' sugary, just for you
So sweet, got a crush on me
Sugar rush right into you
Not enough of me
Drippin'
So sweet, got a crush on me
Sugar rush